* +1 (307) 429-2003

0Cart 0

* Shop by Brand

* Shop by Category

* Shop by Brand
* Shop by Category

Privacy Policy
==============

* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
--------------

[Support](https://coinmonster.store/author/bradcurrencyhub-io/ "Posts by Support")2021-08-22T05:38:11+00:00

Coin Monster Store
------------------

Currency Hub LLC  
Attn: Coin Monster Store  
30 N. Gould Ave Ste R.  
Sheridan, WY 82801  
+1 (307) 429-2003

**A summary:** Our goal is to collect only enough data to let you view the site properly and to allow you to pay for, & for us to ship the stuff you buy. If you set up an account we store the information you provide but an account is not required. We also collect IP address of anyone who trys to “hack” our site.

If you pay by by credit card we never see or store you card information we just get a token from our payment processor.  
If you pay with cryptocurrency, your transactions are stored on the respective blockchain but we don’t save or share that information.

Our website address is: https://coinmonster.store.

It is Currency Hub LLC’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://coinmonster.store (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “https://coinmonster.store”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

Website Visitors
----------------

Currency Hub LLC may temporarily collects non-**Personal Identifiable Information** (**PII**) of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. We use this data if needed to support our firewall/security efforts.

Gathering of **Personal Identifiable Information** (**PII**)
------------------------------------------------------------

Certain visitors to Currency Hub LLC’s websites choose to interact with Currency Hub LLC in ways that require Currency Hub LLC to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Currency Hub LLC gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://thecurrencyhub.io/ to provide a username and email address.

Security
--------

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Links To External Sites
-----------------------

Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.

Protection of Certain **Personal Identifiable Information** (**PII**)
---------------------------------------------------------------------

Currency Hub LLC discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Currency Hub LLC’s behalf or to provide services available at Currency Hub LLC’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Currency Hub LLC’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Currency Hub LLC will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Affiliate Disclosure
--------------------

This site uses affiliate links and does earn a commission from certain links. This does not affect your purchases or the price you may pay.

Cookies
-------

Currency Hub LLC uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Currency Hub LLC uses cookies to help Currency Hub LLC identify and track visitors, their usage of https://coinmonster.store/, and their website access preferences. Currency Hub LLC visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Currency Hub LLC’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Currency Hub LLC’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Currency Hub LLC’s use of cookies.

E-commerce
----------

Those who engage in transactions with Currency Hub LLC – by purchasing Currency Hub LLC’s services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Currency Hub LLC collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Currency Hub LLC. Currency Hub LLC does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Privacy Policy Changes
----------------------

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Currency Hub LLC may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Currency Hub LLC’s sole discretion. Currency Hub LLC encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Share this post

 [](https://coinmonster.store/ "Coin Monster Store - Dive into Coin Monster, the leading ecommerce platform for cryptocurrency branded products. From Bitcoin tees to Ethereum mugs, discover premium quality crypto merchandise. Shop now!")CoinMonster.Store © Copyright 2023 Currency Hub LLC. All Rights Reserved.

**Bitcoin**Black Friday, get 20% off your entire order! [Dismiss](#)

Select your currency
